Guide to the Division of Student Affairs Records RG 5
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- 8. Student Affairs
  - General A - P
    - National Association of Foreign Student Advisors (NAFSA): Boot Camp 1995, Professional Reference Manual (Box 13, Folder 41-45)
    - National Association of Foreign Student Advisors (NAFSA): The Immigration Advisor, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 46-47)
    - National Association of Foreign Student Advisors (NAFSA): The Immigration Quarterly, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 48-50)
    - National Association of Foreign Student Advisors (NAFSA): International Student Handbook, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - NASFAA Videoconference, October 15, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - National Health & Awareness Services (NHA) Campus Student Assistance Program, undated (Box 13, Folder 53-58)
    - NEASC (New England Association of Schools and Colleges), 1992-1994 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - NEASC (New England Association of Schools and Colleges): Self Study, Comprehensive Overview, 1983-1988 (Box 13, Folder 60-64)
    - NEASC (New England Association of Schools and Colleges): Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - NEASC (New England Association of Schools and Colleges): Final Report, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 2-4)
    - NEASC (New England Association of Schools and Colleges): Steering Committee Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
    - New Student Directory, 1965-1989 (Box 20-21)
    - New Student Orientation Bulletin, 1987-1988 (Box OS 2)
    - New Student Orientation, 1953-1954, 1972-2000 (Box 14, Folder 7-49)
    - Non-Traditional Student Cabinet, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Observations on Growing Paints at WCSC by Harold R. Burke, Dean, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Personal Safety 101 On Campus (cassette tape), 1990 (Box 18)
    - Policies and Procedures, 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 52-55)
    - Program Sheets for the Academic Year 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 56-57)
    - Programs and Services, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Publications, 1978-2000 (Box 14, Folder 59-64)
  - General R - Z
    - Registrar's Reports, 1989-1991 (Box 16, Folder 35-38)
    - Retention Committee (bulk 1989), 1984-1990 (Box 16, Folder 39-43)
    - Retention, Class of 1981 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Retention-WCSU 1981 Survey (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Retention-Freshmen 1981 Report (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Retention-Krause Study, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Retention-WCSU Kreizinger Report, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Retention-WCSU 1985 Report (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Retention, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - School Song (DNS), 1926 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Sourcebook: Promising Practices: Campus Alcohol Strategies, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 52-53)
    - Statement of Account, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Step-Up Program (Summer), 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 55-63)
    - Step-Up Evaluation, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - STING (Students Together Initiating New Growth): Leadership Retreat, 1990-1994 (Box 17, Folder 1-9)
    - Strategic Plan (1992-1998), May 1992 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Strategic School District Profile, 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 11-13)
    - Student Activities Fund Handbook, 1992-1994 (Box 17, Folder 14-16)
    - Student Activity Fund, State's Procedures, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Student Employee Handbook, September 2003 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Student Handbook, 1926-2007 (Box 19, Folder 1-33)
    - Student Leadership Recognition Banquet, 1993-2006 (Box 17, Folder 19-26)
    - Student Rights and Responsibilities, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - A Summer Program Evaluation, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Testing and Counseling, 1965-1969 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Ten Year Analysis General/Extension Funds, 1979-1989 (Box OS 2)
    - Testing-Comprehensive (Freshmen), 1982 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Total Quality Management, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 31-40)
    - University Senate, 1990-1993 (Box 17, Folder 41-43)
    - WESTERN Connecticut State University, (VHS) 2 copies, undated (Box 18, Folder *)
  - Racial and Ethnic Diversity
    - Board of Governors, Strategic Plan for Diversity, 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Board of Governors, Strategic Plan for Diversity, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
    - Celebrating Differences, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Diversity Awareness, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 5-7)
    - Diversity Awareness, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 8-10)
    - Diversity Month, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Access & Retention Plan, 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 13-16)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Board of Governors Update, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Financial Report, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Fiscal Report (Summer 1987 Final), 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Fiscal Report, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Fiscal Report, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Fiscal Report, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Fiscal Report, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Fiscal Report, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Fiscal Report (Final) 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Grant (Summer), 1987 (Box 15, Folder 27-30)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Grant, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): MEIP, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 32-34)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): MEIP, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 35-40)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Strategic Plan Report, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Student Survey - Barnett Study, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 42-43)
    - Minority Enrollment Incentive Program (MEIP): Student Survey - Barnett Study, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 44-47)
    - Plan to Promote Pluralism, 1989-1992 (Box 15, Folder 48-51)
    - Pluralism Plan Update, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 52-53)
    - Racial and Ethnic Diversity, Guide to Institutional Self Study, undated (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Racial & Ethnic Diversity Plan (WCSU), 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 55-56)
    - Racial & Ethnic Diversity Plan (WCSU) Sept. '86, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 57-59)
    - Racial & Ethnic Diversity Plan, 1986-1991 (Box 16, Folder 1-10)
    - Racism on Campus 3/88, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Student Affairs Conference, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 12-19)
    - Task Force on Diversity, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 20-23)
    - Task Force on Diversity, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 24-26)
    - Task Force on Diversity, 1988-1990 (Box 16, Folder 27-31)
    - UCAR (University Committee Against Racism), 1988 (Box 16, Folder 32-34)